A Blast With Both Barrels Blazing!
Dead in Tombstone is a western, action, fantasy film directed by Roel Reiné.
An outlaw named Guerrero Hernandez is shot in the back and killed whilst
attempting to free his half-brother from a small-town prison.
Making a deal with the devil, Hernandez returns
from the dead to take his revenge.
Guerrero, played by Danny Trejo.
Lucifer, played by Mickey Rourke.
Red Hernandez, played by Anthony Michael Hall.
Calathea Massey, played by Dina Meyer.
Jack Sutter, played by Richard Dillane.
Ramos, played by Ronan Summers.
Dead in Tombstone is a 2013 American direct-to-video horror
Western film produced by Universal 1440 Entertainment.
It was directed by Roel Reiné and written by Shane Kuhn and Brendan Cowles.
The film stars Danny Trejo as Guerrero, a gang leader who
gets double-crossed by his fellow gang members.
Striking a pact with the Devil after entering Hell, he resurfaces to the earthly
world to avenge his own death by killing the men who murdered him.
The film was released in home media on October 22, 2013, and was
followed by a sequel, Dead Again in Tombstone (2017).
The film is based on the concept of the deal with the Devil.
The film explores themes of saloon, supernatural, forced labour, hell, revenge.
The tone is dark and emotional.